{
    "id": "057222d07a0f43a8b49e72c5274ce0ca",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. people want a new system.",
            "description": "We use most before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the nicest ……………………… them all.",
            "description": "After superlatives we use of before plurals.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ten times …………………………. difficult than I expected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as much",
                "more",
                "as much more"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It would be better if we …………………………. it the other way up.",
            "description": "When the verb in the if clause is in the simple past tense, we use would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "turn",
                "turned",
                "have turned",
                "had turned"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This doesn’t ……………………… very nice.",
            "description": "The infinitive is used without to after do, does and did.",
            "answers": [
                "taste",
                "tastes",
                "tasting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t like ……………………….. of my grammar teachers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "all"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Either Peter or Jack ……………………… here in the morning.",
            "description": "We use a singular verb after either…or.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m ……………………… a phone call from my boss at",
            "description": "We wait when somebody or something is late. ",
            "answers": [
                "expecting",
                "waiting",
                "hoping"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mumbai is ………………………… away than Bangalore.",
            "description": "Both further and farther can be used to talk about distance.",
            "answers": [
                "farther",
                "further",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I always felt ………………………… when I was with him.",
            "description": "Feel is a copular verb. We use adjectives, not adverbs to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "inferior",
                "inferiorly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………………… to Greece next week.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about personal arrangements.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "are going",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… having a headache, I enjoyed the film.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition and we use a preposition before a noun or an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}